Guide to the Edward A. Feigenbaum Papers SC0340
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Original accession, Accession ARCH-1986-052
  - Articles and papers
    - Frijda, Nico H., articles, 1967-72 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Gagne, Robert M., article (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Garfinkel, Sylvia, "Heuristic solution of First-Year Algebra Problems,", undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Galernter, H., articles, 1960-77 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Gibson, Eleanor, article, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Gilinsky, Alberta A., "The Span of Visual Attention...", undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Glushkov, V., articles, 1963-66 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Goldberger, Lewis R., article (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Goncharenko, M. N., article, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Good, I. J., articles, 1965-68 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Gordon, Barry A., "The Heuristic Model of Thought Processes: An Analysis and Attempted Extension,", 1964 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Gorn, Saul, article, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Green, Cordell, articles, 1968-77 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Greenberger, Martin, article, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Greeno, J. G., article, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Greenwald, I. D., article, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Gregg, L. W., articles, 1966-67 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Gregory, R. L., article, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Grossman, Gregory, article, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Gruenberger, Fred, article, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Grunbaum, article, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Guard, J. R., article, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Guilford, J. P., article, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Gullahorn, John T. and Jeanne E., articles, 1964-65 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Hamming, R. W., "Intellectual Implications of the Computer Revolution,", undated (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Haney, Frederick Marion, dissertation, Carnegie-Mellon, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Hanna, Joseph Ford, articles, 1964-65 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Hansen, Gilbert J., article, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Hansen, Per Brinch, articles with cover letter, 1975-76 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Hansen, Per Brinch, articles published by Information Science California Institute of Technology, 1975-76 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Hardy, Steven, "Automatic Induction of LISP Functions," with comments by others, 1973-74 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Harmon, Leon D., article, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Harrison, Annette, articles, 1966-67 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Haverty, J. P., article, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Hayes, Pat "Nine Deadly Sins" [in AI work], undated (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Hayes-Roth, Barbara and Frederick, papers, 1973-78 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Hays, David G, article, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Hellman, Martin E., article, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Hesse, Mary B., article, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - Hewitt, Carl, articles, undated (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - Hiller, Lejaren, articles, 1965 and undated (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - Hintzman, Douglas, papers, undated (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - Hoggatt, A. C., articles, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - Holland, Wade B., articles, 1963-66 (Box 49, Folder 51)
    - Holt, Anatol W., paper, 1963 (Box 49A, Folder 52)
    - Hormann, Aiko M., article, 1962 (Box 49A, Folder 53)
    - Horowitz, N. H., article, 1967 (Box 49A, Folder 54)
    - Hovland, Carl I., paper (Box 49A, Folder 55)
    - Hunt, Earl, articles (Western Management Science Insitute, UCLA), 1962-66 (Box 49A, Folder 56)
    - Hunt, Earl, articles (Dept. of Psychology, U. of Washington), 1968 (Box 49A, Folder 57)
    - Hunt, Earl, articles, miscellaneous, 1964-73 (Box 49A, Folder 58)
    - Hyman, Ray, articles, 1961-63 (Box 49A, Folder 59)
    - Newell, Allen, 1961-77 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Nielsen, Norman R., 1967-71 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Nilsson, Nils J., 1967-75 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Simon, Herbert A., 1964-68 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - S: miscellaneous articles (Box 51, Folder 5.1)
    - Stanford University Annual report [includes article by John McCarthy], 1967 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Stansfield, Jim (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Stephan, Pat [CDRP Translations], 1966 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Sussman, Gerald J., 1972 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Sutherland, N. S., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Pople, Harry E. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Pylyshyn, Zenon W. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Rosenfeld, stephen S., 1964-66 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Translations, August 1966 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Sutherland, Georgia [student paper from Feigenbaum class], 1966 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Sweitzer, Dorothy I., 1961 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Swets, John A., 1965 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Articles 2 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Interorgtekhnika-66: text and photos, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 18.1)
    - Miscellaneous Articles 3 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Leon, Alberto, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Lederberg, Joshua, 1964-71 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Lettvin, J. V., 1959 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Levien, Roger, 1964-65 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Licklider, J. C. R. (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Lin, Shen (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Lindsay, Robert K., 1961 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Lindsay, Robert K., 1960 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Loehlin, John C. (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - London, Ralph L., 1964-68 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Lowerre, Bruce T.: The Harpy Speech Recognition System, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Lucas, John, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Luria, A. R., 1964 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Lynn, Richard Shelly (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - MacKay, Donald, 1963-64 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - MACSYMA, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Manna, Zohar, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - March, James G., 1954-60 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Marchand, Maurice, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Maron, M. E., 1961-64 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Abelson, Robert P., 1965-71 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Adams, Ernest W., 1966 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Adelson-Velskiy, G. M. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Aganbegyan, A., 1961 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Allen, T. J., 1965 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Allen-Babcock Computing, RUSH Terminal User's Manual, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Amarel, Saul, 1970-76 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Amarel, Saul, 1968-71 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Amarel, Saul, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Amarel, Saul, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Amarel, Saul, 1966-68 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Anderson, John R., 1977-78 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Anderson, Robert H., 1973 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Anderson, R. A., 1971 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Andreae, J. H., 1968 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Anokhin, P. K., 1962 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Armer, Paul, 1962-75 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Ashby, W. Ross, 1962-63 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Atkinson, Richard C., 1963-72 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Baker, C. L., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Balderston, F. E., 1960 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Balderston, F. E., 1961 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Bales, Robert F., 1951 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Balzer, R. M., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Balzer (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Banerji, Ranan B. (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Baran, Paul, 1971-73 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Barnett, J. A., 1977 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Barstow, David "A Knowledge-Based System for Automatic Program Construction.", 1977 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Bastin, E. W., 1961 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Batov, Ivan, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Bell, Gordon, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Battig, William F., 1961-63 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Benkard, J. Philip, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Bennett, Edward L., 1964 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Berliner, Hans, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Bernstein, aLEX (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Binford, Thomas O. (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Bledsoe, W., 1971 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Bobrow, Daniel G., 1963 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Boehm, B. W., 1972 (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Boden, Margaret A., 1973 (Box 54, Folder 42)
    - Bolles, Robert, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - Botvinnik, Mikhail, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - Bower, Gordon, 1963 (Box 54A, Folder 45)
    - Bower, Gordon, 1966 (Box 54A, Folder 46)
    - Bower, Gordon H., 1969-70 (Box 54A, Folder 47)
    - Brown, Roger, 1966 (Box 54A, Folder 48)
    - Brazier, Mary A. B., 1964 (Box 54A, Folder 49)
    - Broadbent, D. E., 1965 (Box 54A, Folder 50)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Urie, 1962 (Box 54A, Folder 51)
    - Brown, John Seely, 1958, 1977 (Box 54A, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence
    - AAUP (American Association of University Professors) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ACM (Association for Computing Machinery) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ACME Notes (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - ACME Utilization Budgets (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - AI Handbook (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - AI Journal (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - AFIPS (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - AI Internal Briefing Document (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - AIM/SUMEX (User Community) (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Stanford SUMEX/AIM (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - AIM Advisory Committee (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - AMAREL's Comments on IFIP Paper (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Amarel, Feigenbaum, Newell Book (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Applied Math (Dept. of) (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - American Nuclear Society Conference (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - American Scientist (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Anderson, R. H. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Applied Spectroscopy Review (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Aquino, Jean-Anne (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - ARPA (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - ARPA Project Quarterly Reports (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - ARPA Proposal, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - ARPA Correspondence File (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - ARPA Project Univ. of Calif., Berkeley (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - ARPA Time-Sharing Proposal, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - ARPA Proposal, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - ARPANET (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - ARPA--Office Automation (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - ARPA Report, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - ARPA Space (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - ARPA-SRI Proposal (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - ARPA-West (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Artificial Intelligence, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Artificial Intelligence--1973 Minsky # 2 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Artificial Intelligence NASA Report, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Artificial Intelligence Lectures (Feigenbaum) (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Artificial Intelligence: Themes in The Second Decade (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Artificial Intelligence Project Quarterly Reports (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Assistantship Inquiries (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - AUI Project (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Automated Bio-Lab: A Proposal Leiderberg/McCarthy (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Automatic Programming Conference, Jan. 1973 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Automation Project (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Avionics Panel (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Barth--Grants (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Basic Research on Advanced Memory Systems for Computers - AMT (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Beel, C. Gordon (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Bibliographies (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Blaisdell Paper, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Bowman, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Bowman Alumni (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Allen Brown (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Dennis Brown's Thesis (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Bruce Buchanan--Vita (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Roberts/Dorman/Carhart (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Calendar, EAF, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Carbonnel, Dr. Jaime R. (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence--John Allen (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - EAF Correspondence 1972 and 1973 (A-L) (Box 19, Folder 3.1)
    - EAF Correspondence 1972 and 1973 (M-Z) (Box 19, Folder 3.2)
    - EAF Correspondence 1975/1976 (A-L) (Box 19, Folder 4.1)
    - EAF Correspondence 1975/1976 (M-Z) (Box 19, Folder 4.2)
    - EAF Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence A (1 of 2), 1963-71 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence A (2 of 2), 1961-67 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence B (1 of 2), 1961-71 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence B (2 of 2), 1959-67 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence B, 1975-76 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence C, 1964-71 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence D, 1968-71 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence E, 1967-70 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence F, 1967-71 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence G, 1968-71 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence H, 1967-70 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence I-J, 1968-71 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence K, 1964-70 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence L, 1968-71 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence Mc, 1968-70 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence M, 1968-71 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence N, 1964-71 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence O, 1962-69 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence P, 1959-71 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence Q, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence R (1 of 2), 1966-70 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence R (2 of 2), 1963-67 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence S (1 of 3), 1968-71 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence S (2 of 3), 1960-70 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence S (3 of 3), 1960-67 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence T, 1965-71 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence U-V, 1962-71 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence W, 1963-71 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence Y-Z, 1961-71 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Computer Printout [text]: Feb. 1 and Feb. 3, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Computer Printout [text]: Oct. 28, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Message.Txt. Printout: Dec. 14, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Message.Txt. Printout: July 28, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Message.Txt. Printout: Feb. 28--March 1, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Message.Txt. Printout: Oct. 11, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Message.Txt. Printout: April 18, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Old Messages to Review/ Contains Milestones ala Russell (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Message.Txt March 13, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Message.Txt. March 21, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Message.Txt. August 3, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Message.Txt. July 27, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Message.Txt. Sept. 18 and Sept. 14, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Message.Txt. Sept. 5, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Message.Txt. March 27, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Message.Txt. Dec. 13, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Message.Txt. Dec. 20, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Message.Txt. Dec. 9, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 17.1)
    - Message.Txt. Nov. 6 and Nov. 10, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Message.Txt. Nov. 20, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 18.1)
    - Message.Txt. Oct. 24 and Oct. 19, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Message.Txt. Oct. 9, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Message.Txt. Sept. 26, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Message.Txt. March 14, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Message.Txt. March 1, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Message.Txt. Jan. 31 and Feb. 20, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Message.Txt. Feb. 27, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Message.Txt. Feb. 16, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Message.Txt. Feb. 15, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Message.Txt. Feb. 12, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Message.Txt. Feb. 9, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Message.Txt. Feb. 7 and Feb. 1-2, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Message.Txt. Jan. 24, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Message.Txt. Jan. 19, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Message.Txt. Jan. 12, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Message.Txt. Jan. 4, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Message.Txt. Jan. 4, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Message.Txt. May 11, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Message.Txt. June 10, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Message.Txt. May 25, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Message.Txt. May 14, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Message.Txt. May 7, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - April 29, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - March 25, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - March 22, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - March 22, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - March 14, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - January 12, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - July 1, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - June 19, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - June 15, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - April 1, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - April 20, 1979 mail (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - July 3, 1980 mail (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - June 30, 1980 mail (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - June 21, 1980 mail (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - April 23, 1980 mail (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - May 16, 1980 mail (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - February 13, 1978 mail (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - February 15, 1978 mail (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - February 12, 1978 mail (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Two printouts: Criteria for Distributed Computation by Gio Wiederhold, 1977; list of Feigenbaum files (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Bryan, G. E. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Feldman, J. A. 75- (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Burstall, R. M. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Fike 1- (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Burstyn 1 [EMPTY] (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Findler 1- (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - CABAL (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Format Sample (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Carbonnel, Jaime G (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Flock 1- (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Carroll, J. B. 1- (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Carroll, J. D. 1- (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Chenzoff 1- (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Churchman 1-6 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Churchman 21- (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Churchman (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Citrenbaum (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Clarke 25- (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Clarkson 5- (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Codd, E. F. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Cohen, H. (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Colby 1- (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Colby, Kenneth Mark (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Coles, S. (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Corey, Elias J. (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Cooper 1- (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Crossman 1- (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Crosson 50 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Cyert 8- (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Daley 1- (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Davis, Randall, "Production Rules As A Representation For A Knowledge-Based Consultation Program" (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Deffenbacher, K. (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Delfino (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Denton 1- (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Dingman 1- (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Doig 2 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Domolky 1- (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Doran J. (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Dreyfus, H. (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Dupchak (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Eastman 1- (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - Eavarone, D. S. (Box 52, Folder 37)
    - Edwards 1-5 (Box 52, Folder 38)
    - Edwards 6-10 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Engelbart (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - Ernst, Barbara (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - Ernst, H 1- (Box 52, Folder 42)
    - Ershov (Box 52, Folder 43)
    - Evans 5- (Box 52, Folder 44)
    - Feigenbaum (Box 52, Folder 45)
    - Feldman, J. 1-3 (Box 52, Folder 46)
    - Feldman, J. 4- (Box 52, Folder 47)
    - Marr, D. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Mexico City 8/67 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Marschak 1-8 [Empty] (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - MI-5 Machine Intelligence Workshop 5 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Marschak 9- (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - MI-6 Machine Intelligence Workshop 6 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Marschak, T. A. 50- (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - MI-7 Machine Intelligence Workshop 7 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - March, James G. and Johan P. Olsen in A Garbage Can Model of Organizational Choice (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Michie, Donald (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - March, James G. and Johan P. Olsen in The Uncertainty of the Past: Organizational Learning Under Ambiguity (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Microfilm Output (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Masterman 1- (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - John Miller (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Mathews 1- (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - University of Missouri-Columbia National Advisory Council on Health Services Research Center (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - John McCarthy (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - National Advisory Council Meeting Columbia, Missouri June 12-13, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - McGaugh 1-14 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - National Advisory Council Meeting Palo Alto, California February 23-24, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - McGaugh 15- (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Mitchell Model (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Mehler, J. (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Molecular Genetics (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Melton 1- (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Meltzer, B. (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Meyer, A. (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Michael 1- (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Michie, D. (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Michie, Donald Book Review of "Computer Power and Human Reason: From Judgement to Calculation" by J. Weizenbaum (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Miller 1- (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Millstein 50- (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Minsky 1- (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Minsky 10- (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Mitroff 1- [Empty] (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Mooers 1- (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - McCarthy 1- (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - McCulloch 1- (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Neisser 1- (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Newell, Allen "Fairytales" (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Newell 1-3 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Newell 4-8 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Newell 9-10 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Newell 11-12 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Newell 13-17 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Newell 18-20 [Empty] (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Newell 21-õó24 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Newell 25-27 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Newell 28- (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Newell 33- (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Mathematical Social Sciences Board (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - MAC (Project MAC) (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Management Information System (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Management Science Laboratory University of California, Berkeley (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Masinter, Larry (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - McGraw-Hill PL-1 Manuscript (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - McGraw-Hill Series (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Memory Models Book (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Project files
    - Feigenbaum and Feldman, Computers and Thought, Vol. 2, source material (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Computers and Thought, Vol. 2, Working Paper Nos. 1-3 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - "Rational Decisionmaking in Business Organizations" by H. A. Simon and "On Cybernetics, Information Processing and Thinking" by M. E. Maron (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - IBM lawsuit (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - CDC deposition (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - IBM-CDC lawsuit materials: "A Comparison of the Simplex and Semi-duplex Configurations for the IBM 360/67" by K. R. Graham; "Evaluating Time-Shared Computer Usage," Michael M. Gold, May 1966; and correspondence, 1966-67 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Computing at FERMILAB 1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - GEO (French project, lecture notes) 1980-81 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Vuegraphs for TEKNOWLEDGE 1982-83 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Minsky's Appendix A to Computers and Thought (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Early Lederberg (Joshua) papers (NASA) 1964-65 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - SUMEX background material 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Lenat's thesis work on AM (slides) (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Art of artificial intelligence (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Slides, miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Slides, miscellaneous group 2 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - All-day seminar on expert systems developed for TEKNOWLEDGE (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - HPP material (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Transparancies, Board of Trustees, March 7, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Larry Fogan, VM thesis work (notes) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Clancy's thesis work (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - 'Puff' slide [medical automated instrument] (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Ventilator Manager (VM) by Larry Fagan 1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - DENDRAL/CONGEN material 1976 and undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - CLOT 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - "Applications for Artificial Intelligence for Chemical Inference - XXI" by Cheer, C., Djerassi, C., et al 1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - MOLGEN (Friedland's work) (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - GUIDON slides (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - MOLGEN slides (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - MOLGEN slides (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - "Planning with Constraints" by Mark Stefik 1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - MOLGEN slides, Stefik's work (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - EMYCIN (1 transparency) (Box 4, Folder 33)